Rock on to Su-san's heart! We are CHO!
Tokimeki-Sendem!
Nice to meet you!
I'm so happy!
I'm happy too!
I'm Su from Silent Siren. Nice to meet
you!
Nice to meet you!
Thank you!
It feels like a feast.
Everyone watching the Toki-Sen Rock On
channel!
Hello! Nice to meet you! I'm Su from
Silent Siren's vocal guitar!
I'm Su from Silent Siren's vocal
guitar!
I can't stop this feeling!
I made a song called LOVE.
I chose the words that would be cute if
these girls sang and sang these words.
I chose the words while imagining the
part that was pulled out by the monitor
during the live performance.
I made it a song that could be loved by
fans.
I made a lot of words called LOVE and
wrote the lyrics.
It's really cute.
I can't express it.
The cuteness and purity.
It's pink. It's a song full of love.
It's fun to sing live.
I got a call in me.
Like this.
Is it a hint?
My favorite part is...
No one is with me right now.
I like this kind of song.
I think it will be exciting with the PR
manager.
So, please look forward to it.
When I hear this song, my heart will be
full of tears.
I'll give it back to you.
It's a good song that makes me feel
excited.
Please look forward to it.
I can't decide which lyrics are my
favorite.
It's a very cute lyrics.
I like that part.
You laugh like this.
I've never heard the word like this.
I'm like this.
I think it's a wonderful lyrics.
I want you to listen to it soon.
What?
Something...
Go ahead.
You can go this way.
Oh, this way.
I'm going.
Is it love?
No, it's not.
What's wrong?
How many times have I said love?
Thank you!
I sang with a lot of effort.
When I was talking, I said,
I've never seen anyone say,
I'm in love.
I used to say,
I shouldn't have spilled a little bit.
I was singing alone in a small room.
Maybe it's a good thing.
This song.
I sang alone.
Thank you!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Sui of Silent Silent.
I was really happy to get this offer.
And I got an image of this kind of
thing.
I was really happy about that.
I was able to write lyrics with fun.
I'm going to finish this recording.
I'm looking forward to seeing this song
live.
I'm looking forward to delivering it to
everyone.
Please look forward to it.
The recording was already really cute.
It's the best.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you!
Really?
I've been watching your Instagram.
I was really looking forward to it.
I was thinking,
I was doing a song with a songwriter.
I thought it was a really good song.
I thought it was unfair.
Please subscribe to my channel!
You know, right? I want you
More than anyone, I'll always
love you, that's for sure
Yeah yeah!
Tara tara tara tara tara tara tara
Boom boom tarara tarara tarara
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Tara tara tara tara tara tara
Boom boom tarara tarara tarara
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
It's our own IZONE!